what's up guys so this video is going to
be an honest opinion about what I think
about this new hair product I found at
Walmart
it's called it's a 10 miracle leave-in
plus keratin it's supposed to be like a
leave-in conditioner I have not being
paid at all nor did I receive mr. Frese
I paid about $20 for fluid ounces of
this stuff at Walmart so my expectations
are kind of high if you are wanting to
see what my honest opinion is stay tuned
and we will get to that so okay so this
is my hair on the wash day it is kind of
frizzy very curly as you can see this is
fresh out of a messy bun so it's it's
very curly you can kind of see the
texture up close lots of curl lots of
frizz especially up here at the top okay
so my hair is freshly washed
I just shampooed and conditioned I
haven't put anything in it or brushed it
out and will read the directions on what
this product says to do and see how it
goes it says it is for all hair types so
that's awesome
it helps replace loss protein protects
the natural keratin and the hair
protects against heat which is awesome
seals cuticles for extra silky hair
detangles deep frizzes and add shine
restores hydration balance so lots of
good things for my hair type but my
problem is I love to wear my hair down
but my hair once it dries it gets really
frizzy and kind of goofy wiry just
unmanageable so will read the directions
on this bottle it says it's amazingly
easy to use shampoo and condition hair
towel dry and spray products all over
hair and come through so we will go
ahead and do that okay
there we go you wanna see the texture of
it this is one spritz on my hand it's
not like a it's almost like a cream
actually yeah I was gonna say it wasn't
like a cream but it's a more like a
serum mixed with the cream type texture
I'm gonna make sure to get my ends
really good a lot of my frizz kind of
starts up here at the top what's also
great about this product one of the
reasons I was okay with spinning so much
on it is not only is it Aleve in oh well
well so that definitely helps detangle
for my hair that is really smooth and
quick to brush out I'm gonna start at
the bottom of the rest of it kind of see
how it goes that it's really really easy
I can definitely tell the difference
from my hair with how easily this is
just sliding right through all the
tangles normally I have to work through
a lot there is a tangle right there and
it's already done the smell is it's not
very strong on the hair once you spray
it on
[Music]
it's not a very it's not a very strong
smell it does smell good it's not
overwhelming a lot of hair products can
get really overwhelming with this smell
smell for me and it's just a real subtle
real subtle not even more like flowery
rather than fruity it's okay so my hair
is brushed out and the product is
sprayed through and then the product was
brushed through and what I noticed it
was a lot easier to brush a lot easier
to the tangle it added I can tell
there's a lot more shine in my hair even
though it is still wet there's more
shine there than there normally is which
is awesome I'm gonna let my hair air dry
normally that's what my normal routine
is and then I'll get back with you guys
and show you what it looks like air
dried
naturally alright I'll let my hair
completely air dry naturally and wow
this is awesome
there is a lot less frizz than I usually
experience with my hair there's like a
gloss a little Sheen to it I'm not sure
if you can see that very well it's not
heavy
a lot of moisturizing products and like
frizz creams and stuff like that is
really heavy and kind of like Oh once
you whenever you touch it but this is
like I love it you can definitely tell
that I have something in my hair it's
not like there's no product at all but
it's not like a bad product feel the
curls are nice and soft they're not
weighted down they're still they're
still bouncy so it is on the pricier
side for what I would normally buy from
your products but with these results I
can wear my hair down just like this or
do like half-up half-down and I wouldn't
have to worry about the frizz or looking
crazy and gnarly or Y rly wiry at all so
this product is a win for me just for
the detangling factor that's awesome if
it helps with split ends that still yet
to be seen we'll figure that out I like
this product I like this product so far
and I have my bathroom if you guys could
see my cabinets it's full of hair creams
and moisturizers and leave-in
conditioners and all this yada yada yada
but a lot of them I have problems with
because it's weighted down it makes it
feel sticky I don't like the way that it
makes my hair look or it just doesn't
help with the frizz at all and my hair
is naturally very frizzy so for it to
look like this and it has had no heat in
it whatsoever
it's just all's I did was spray this
product in it after I took a shower this
is this is really really good for my
hair very very good so yeah this is a
it's not a pic promotional is it just my
honest opinion is it worth twenty
dollars for me and my hair and what it
just did for me I would say yes I can
wear my hair down like this or I can put
it into a half up half down or whatever
I wanted to do and it would look good so
on a scale of one to ten for its
attendant I would rate this probably a
nine I like it I like it quite a bit and
I am very picky with hair products
because of the type of hair that I have
and how hard it is to make happy so if
the ten definitely did it for me super
impressed would recommend if you guys
have curly frizzy damaged hair any of
the above that give it a try and see
what you think films so if you guys
liked this video give it a big thumbs up
hit that subscribe button and make sure
to turn on your notification so you are
aware of when my next video is posted